<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Devil&#39;s Avocado</title>
        <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Devil&#39;s Avocado</description>

         
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>2025 Is Definitely a Number</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/december-2024-january-2025/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 12:42:01 -0600</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2025 is definitely a number.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Fall 2024</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/fall-2024/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 06:53:00 -0600</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;October is a time of year. Oh yes, it is.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the time of year to go to a pumpkin patch with cousins while the cousin&amp;rsquo;s mom (Janae) deals with complications from having a baby (Penny). It all turned out ok (SPOILER ALERT).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Summer 2024</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/summer-2024/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 03:41:10 -0500</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Summer 2024. It was one for the ages. Emily went to Utah for 2 months and I stayed in Oklahoma. In July, I went on a road trip. First stop, Durango where I met up with my parents, Shauni and Jordan, Megan and Todd, and their respective families. We did Durango things. Rafting, ruins, ice cream, dinner and a show, mountain biking. That sorta thang.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Spring 2024 Stuff</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/spring-2024/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 16:04:06 -0500</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;In March, my parents visited from Arizona. We took them to nowhere Oklahoma to eat some yummy food and go to a museum. The restaurant we were going to go to had an hour-long wait time so we settled for some yummy pizza, with which we were not disappointed at all.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>January 2024 and some older stuff</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/january-and-stuff/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 12:47:36 -0600</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;hurricane&#34;&gt;Hurricane&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We went on a trip to Hurricane UT which we tend to do twice a year.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even though the temperature hung around 40 degrees Fahrenheit (or 4 degrees Celcius for those who want to use a system that makes sense), Calvin wanted to hang out in the pool for several hours every day.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The pool cover also makes a good driving surface.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://family.dallincoons.com/january-and-stuff/calvinpoolcover.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve introduced Calvin to bowling, which is a great cold-weather activity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Mushroom Trip Two</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/2023-19-2023-mushroom-trip-two/</link>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 03:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;9/3/2023&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was lying on the couch inside the house. I realized the mushrooms were beginning to take effect when I looked out the window at the clouds and saw a bright white cloud peaking up over a mass of gray clouds. For a second I was certain I was looking at the top of a mountain peak.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I continued looking at the clouds, I began seeing shapes form in the clouds. I saw dinosaurs move past, and then three kids playing together, and then a giraffe head. My guide suggested I move outside to which I agreed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>2023 Wrapped</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/2023-wrapped/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 07:18:46 -0600</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, we’re all another year closer to death.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve been in Oklahoma for a year now. I wouldn’t say it feels like home the same way the hot, dry desert in the Southwest does, but it’s nice nonetheless.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>End of Summer</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/end-of-summer/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 19:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Emily has been attending dance class and has been working on a performance inspired by the Barbie movie. Watch the video here and see if you can spot her:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>More June 2023</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/more-june-2023/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 18:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s nifty about where we live is that a berry farm is right down the road where can go pick fresh blueberries and blackberries, but 20 minutes away is a big-ish city.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>November 2022 - June 2023</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/november-2022-june-2023/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 23:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;In November we travelled to visit Owasso, Oklahoma to visit Janae and go house viewing. Calvin got to play with his cousins and we got a reprieve from the bitter Rexburg winter. The fact that we could actually go outside for more than 5 minutes without cursing our very existence was a good sign (also with the way the housing market was going in Idaho, pay a premium for the priveledge).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>(If) I Went On a Mushroom Trip</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/if-i-went-on-a-mushroom-trip/</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 03:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;I, seeking greater enlightenment, embarked on a journey.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had a guide with me who was there to be there with me to help me through the experience and who was able to write my thoughts and insights as I verbally expressed them. My trip was not what I was expecting. I was anticipating that I would put on my headphones and experience music on an entirely new level.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Instead, I experienced &lt;em&gt;trees&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>August - October 2022</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/august-october-2022/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 18:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve built up quite a montage of Calvin playing with cars and trucks and digging in dirt. I think we&amp;rsquo;ve identified his favorite activity, and one of our favorite activities is taking redundant pictures of his cuteness. He also humors us and goes on hikes (eh, more like nature walks), but maybe that&amp;rsquo;s because he knows we always have some trucks stashed away to play with. On our walks, we often stumble upon highly diggable dirt and those come in handy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Summer 2022</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/summer-2022/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Kev&amp;rsquo;s been spending a lot of time doing what he loves to do most.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;play with cars&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;play with trucks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;look at cars&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;look at trucks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;request that we talk about cars and trucks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Calvin</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/calvin/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 19:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This might seem like it&amp;rsquo;s coming out of the blue but we&amp;rsquo;re changing Kevin&amp;rsquo;s name to Calvin. We&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about this since almost the day he was born.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When we were picking a name during pregnancy for the life of us we couldn&amp;rsquo;t decide on a name for a boy that we liked. Ramone was our favorite, but we were reluctant to use what traditionally is a Hispanic name as his first name. Additionally, we (mostly Emily) were concerned about trying to incorporate a family name. We thought about using the name Don(ald) but President 45, who we weren&amp;rsquo;t particular fans of, ruined that idea for us. We wanted a name that would go with Ramone and since we &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; fans of my dad we went with &amp;lsquo;Kevin Ramone&amp;rsquo; which has a nice ring to it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>A Dude Named Dallin</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/a-dude-named-dallin/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 19:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hobbies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve loved collecting vinyl, much of it from criminally obscure bands who only pressed 300 copies of a record in 2014 or whatever. A part of me thinks of record collecting as ‘archiving’. You might ask why I collect vinyl if I can hear the music on the internet. Or you might not ask, in which case I will give the answers unsolicited.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Vinyl sounds better than the compressed digital counterpart sent via electrical pulses through wires. You can actually see the album artwork too.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I seem to be nearly incapable of listening to an entire album on the internet. I get distracted, my player of choice is shuffling before I realize it, and I get distracted. I also get distracted. There’s something about the ritual of pulling out a chunky piece of vinyl that is not only viscerally satisfying but also commits me to listen to a continuous piece of music the way the artists intended. Songs on an album are often sequenced in a way such that the sum of greater than it’s parts. One example I can think of is Black Sabbath’s &lt;em&gt;Master of Reality&lt;/em&gt; when the second to last song &lt;em&gt;Solitude&lt;/em&gt; quietly invokes images of a large starry desert night sky, proceeded by the last song &lt;em&gt;Into the Void&lt;/em&gt; with one the most monstrous, kick-ass riffs in rock n’ roll. That transition is such a good moment, one which can only be experienced through the album format.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Not all records I’ve bought can be easily found or accessed on the interwebs. I recently heard a song called Let Them Eat Valium on a weekly late-night radio show from LA that plays a lot of crazy, weird, and obscure stuff. This song about knocked me over, and I was compelled to track it down. The problem was that the only thing I could find on the internet was a youtube video - of someone playing their vinyl record. I researched the song and discovered that nobody really knows much about the band, who put out one single on a 7” decades ago before sinking back into the darkness of obscurity and nearly being lost in history until someone found a copy at a yard sale and began spreading the word. There are probably a few hundred copies of this record in existence - and might I stress that the song is damn good. Luckily I was able to find a copy, for under 15 bucks too! It’s kind of cool to have an obscure song nobody has ever heard of that’s actually quite catchy.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recently discovered a band from the mid-2000s that I truly believe could have radio hits, even today (maybe add in a little bit of autotune for the kids; and yes, new vinyl is being pressed to this day). I’ve been a little obsessed with them and found myself scouring the internet for a reasonably priced record that is inevitably out of print and few have ever heard of. A few weeks ago I walked into a record store and saw just the record I was looking for, for 7 bucks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>A Boy Named Kev</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/a-boy-named-kev/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 20:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2021/12/img_1825.jpg?w=768&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kev is still learning to talk and the words he uses don&amp;rsquo;t sound like the words we use, but we&amp;rsquo;ve learned to pick up on which of his sounds equates to words we use. Here&amp;rsquo;s a sampling of sounds and their associated words:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bwow! - (probably his favorite word) means truck, car, or any kind of vehicle with wheels really.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Me! - help me!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ball - ball&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Eh - egg&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Why I Don&#39;t Want To Go To Church</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/why-i-dont-want-to-go-to-church/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 02:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;I was baptized a member of The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints when I was 8 years old, which is the Catholic equivalent of being baptized as an infant, and I have been a faithful member for most of my life since then. The LDS church is not just a church to attend on Sunday. It’s a lifestyle that governs many, if not most, aspects of one&amp;rsquo;s life. All of my major life decisions have been influenced by my belief in the teachings of the church.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>January 2021 Deserts and Development</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/january-2021-deserts-and-development/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 02:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;January has historically been the toughest month of the year, at least the years where we&amp;rsquo;ve lived somewhere cold. The thrill of Christmas has gone the way of the carbonation in a flat, half-finished can of coke and the road to spring looks arduous and cold. Emily might seem nice and all, but as long as I&amp;rsquo;ve known her she has had a deep, abiding hatred in her heart for snow. Indeed, our ideal location is somewhere in the beautiful desolation of a warm desert with NO SNOW. We&amp;rsquo;re not totally sure where that is, but wherever it is we&amp;rsquo;d prefer to &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; we&amp;rsquo;re living in the desert, not just a city with hot sidewalks (like the center of Phoenix). We would love to live somewhere with big starry nights, open desert land, and ABSOLUTELY NO SNOW. But that&amp;rsquo;s just a dream at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Beware the Moral Monopoly</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/beware-the-moral-monopoly/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 21:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;There is the way life works and there is the way I wish life worked. This is how I wish it worked: if you have good intentions, you are guaranteed to make good decisions. However, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take much imagination to produce scenarios where this isn&amp;rsquo;t the case. For example, I may have good intentions to fix my friend&amp;rsquo;s car, but unless I&amp;rsquo;ve gained knowledge in car mechanics somewhere along the way, I may actually do more harm than good. Or I may have good intentions by giving an alcoholic family member money when this could likely be enabling bad behavior. This is also very applicable to politics. A politician claiming better intent than an opponent does not automatically mean proposed policies will make the world a better place, and in fact could be utterly counterproductive.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>The End of a Year, 2020 edition</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/the-end-of-a-year-2020-edition/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 18:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Several months ago I wrote about my job search, and some of the failures along the way. In September, I was brought on board to SpotOn as a software engineer, using a language called Go. This is a language I&amp;rsquo;m new to but is one that I was very interested in gaining more experience in. At least 6 months before I started this job I read a book about Go and started solving programming puzzles through a website called &lt;a href=&#34;http://exercism.io&#34;&gt;exercism.io&lt;/a&gt; which has volunteer mentors to help you learn a language. I also started building an app for analyzing expected moves in the stock market using Go. In the end, this was enough for me to land a job. This the formula I&amp;rsquo;ve used to find employment in software engineering without a college degree:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Trepidations of a Parent, One Year later</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/trepidations-of-a-parent-one-year-later/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 22:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a common type of social media post, most typically from parents of small children. You know the ones. Parents are overflowing with gratitude and positivity. I have no reason to doubt the authenticity of such posts. However, I don&amp;rsquo;t believe they adequately capture the full spectrum of the wellspring of emotion that comes with being a parent.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a parent (as of one year ago) so I can say with some first-hand knowledge that sometimes you do feel an extra measure of gratitude and joy, but more often life just as glamorous and romantic as it usually isn&amp;rsquo;t. For some, I imagine candor about the negative aspect of parenthood might seem selfish or overly despondent. However, I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s wise to brush reality under the rug and pretend that parenthood is a perpetual Christmas card family portrait. Prospective parents should be given as much information as possible about what to expect after they&amp;rsquo;re done expecting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Boundaries</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/boundaries/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 03:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Boundaries, a book by Henry Cloud and John Townsend, makes me wonder what percentage of human malcontent is a direct result of some level of inappropriate boundaries. The subject of boundaries is a meaty one as I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered, but I will sample a few specifics of what I found to be the most thought-provoking ideas:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Having appropriate boundaries in our lives means having the discernment to know when to say &amp;rsquo;no&amp;rsquo; and when to say &amp;lsquo;yes&amp;rsquo;, which is fundamental to healthy, fulfilling, and mutually beneficial relationships.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Hurric-uns and hiatuses</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/hurric-uns-and-hiatuses/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 20:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;In August we traveled to Hurric-un (it&amp;rsquo;s a hick Utah pronunciation - just go with it) for the annual family vacation on Emily&amp;rsquo;s side.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To kick things off right, we did the nerdiest thing you could possibly do other than larping. Dungeons and Dragons, which all we all know, is Satan&amp;rsquo;s game. This is what it looks like to be sucked into the occult.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Kitten Forever</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/kitten-forever/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Emily and I have a lot of overlap in our music tastes. While I have more of a tendency to roam into the heavier music, and I seem to have a greater affinity for ska and reggae than she does, we both enjoy much of the same things. One of the bands that we both love is a band called Screaming Females.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Screaming Females is a great band name, but a bit of a misnomer. While the band is indeed fronted by a female, the other two people in the band are dudes. Also, there&amp;rsquo;s no screaming; at least not very much.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Fun With Failure</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/fun-with-failure/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a fantastic time to try and find a new job, and so I&amp;rsquo;m taking full advantage of these flourishing economic times. It certainly helps that I&amp;rsquo;m trying to switch to a new programming language and I&amp;rsquo;m going for a bit of a salary increase.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing a lot of interviewing lately, and it&amp;rsquo;s been interesting to see the different interview styles. Software engineering interviews are always different but still have some common characteristics. For example, they don&amp;rsquo;t ask or seem to care about academic credentials, and there is always a code challenge of some sort.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Kev and Kin</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/kev-and-kin/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 16:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We started feeding Kev solid foods, though it doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem like much of it goes to the correct location. Still, it&amp;rsquo;s good for him to practice, and at the very least it seems like he enjoys playing with all the interesting textures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a video of him trying solid food for the first time. We now let him play with his food, which means he gets really messy and disgusting, and so we make sure to eat dinner right before bath time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Ambitions and Achievements</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/ambitions-and-achievements/</link>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 04:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;rsquo;t written a proper monthly update since July of 2018, which is almost 2 years ago. Time has been a very limited resource lately, and so I&amp;rsquo;ll make that my official excuse. Yeah, that&amp;rsquo;s it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have been feeling the itch to start blogging again, although I&amp;rsquo;m not yet sure exactly what form it will take. The monthly updates are fun, but I also would like to write more &amp;ldquo;big idea&amp;rdquo; kind of stuff, and sometimes I just want to talk about me, which is what most of this post will probably consist of. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll just let inertia have it&amp;rsquo;s way with me, and I&amp;rsquo;ll do precisely nothing. But in all seriousness, blogging really is time consuming, and time is the most precious resource in the world to me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Grief and Gratitude Part 2</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/grief-and-gratitude-part-2/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Kev was born on 7:11, Tuesday morning, after a greuling 48-hour marathon. For the remainer of the day, we had visitors and nurses coming to our room every 30 minutes to poke and prod kev, give us advice, give Emily medicine, poke and prod Kev again, check to see how much he poop he ejected out of his bum, repeated ad naseum.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Grief and Gratitude - Kevin&#39;s birth</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/grief-and-gratitude-kevins-birth/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Our doctor, Dr. Allphin, let us know in one of Emily’s appointments leading up to the due date that he was going to be leaving on vacation for the Thanksgiving holiday. That information coupled with the fact that he didn&amp;rsquo;t want us to go past 41 weeks of pregnancy meant that we might have to make a hard decision. We had never really thought too hard about induction. For some reason, it just didn’t seem like something we needed to worry about or mentally prepare for such a possibility.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>&#34;I&#39;m so excited for you guys&#34; - Trepidations of a soon to be parent</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/im-so-excited-for-you-guys-trepidations-of-a-soon-to-be-parent/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 21:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;People are excited for us to have a child. Are &lt;em&gt;we&lt;/em&gt; excited? It depends on how you define excited I suppose. If we stick to the dictionary definition, &amp;ldquo;stirred emotionally; agitated&amp;rdquo;, then yes, I guess we are excited. Are we excited as in &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not happy and fulfilled until x event happens&amp;rdquo;? Absolutely, unequivocally, no. We&amp;rsquo;re comfortable - perhaps a little too comfortable.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>An Anecdotal Rock and Roll Affair</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/an-anecdotal-rock-and-roll-affair/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 00:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;I work on a computer all day and I had set a reminder to buy tickets to a band called the Distillers, a punk rock band who were reuniting and playing together for the first time in 14 years.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Adventures and adversity (part two)</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/adventures-and-adversity-part-two/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 02:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been struggling with motivation for writing these blog posts. One reason I know for sure is due to how busy we&amp;rsquo;ve been this year. I&amp;rsquo;m working full time, as a software engineer remotely while going to school part-time (a little more than part-time actually).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Adversity and Adventure - 2018 second half (part1)</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/adversity-and-adventure-2018-second-half-part1/</link>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 03:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Oh hey, it&amp;rsquo;s been a while! Oh boy, do we have some stories to tell. So what&amp;rsquo;s new with us? Everything. Everything is different. Let&amp;rsquo;s start from the beginning because I always tell people &amp;ldquo;yeah we&amp;rsquo;re in Idaho, it&amp;rsquo;s a long story&amp;rdquo;. Well here&amp;rsquo;s the long story: In February of 2018, we moved from an apartment in Tempe to a rental house in Phoenix. I knew that it was only a matter of time before I quit my job because I was already at that time getting excruciatingly bored.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Mugs and Monsoons - June/July 2018</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/mugs-and-monsoons-june-july-2018/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 22:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We went to Hurricane for our annual summer vacation with the in-laws, and we had our usual MO of crap tons of board games and quiplash. Oh and this thing almost killed us.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Hipsters and Hinterlands</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/hipsters-and-hinterlands/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 21:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve turned hipster. I have proof. Look: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0520.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0520&#34;&gt; I will now tell you the story about our search for a plant. We went downtown where there&amp;rsquo;s artsy fartsy murals&amp;hellip; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0528.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0528&#34;&gt; And we bought a plant&amp;hellip; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0530.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0530&#34;&gt; The end. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0531.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0531&#34;&gt; There&amp;rsquo;s a band that mentions Arizona sunsets in their song, probably because they look like this: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0547.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0547&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_3812.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3812&#34;&gt; At some point we went to see Lay Mizz (which is how everyone says it) with my bro and his bro (bro as in friend, except for the first one which is in reference to my brother from the same mother). This picture doesn&amp;rsquo;t do the height factor justice, but I was getting some vertigo when we first walked in. And yeah it was pretty fantastic. Not as depressing as I remember (I&amp;rsquo;ve only seen it once which was the most recent movie) &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0567.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0567&#34;&gt; I was woken up at around 2 or 3 am by lots of flashing lights outside and a helicopter circling around the neighborhood. It was quite irritating. Not as irritating as being murdered though, so I&amp;rsquo;m happy it wasn&amp;rsquo;t us who was murdered (I actually don&amp;rsquo;t know what the deal was). I started listening to the police scanner out of morbid curiosity since I wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to sleep with the giant mechanical bird in the sky, but really, police officers need to work on their pronunciation skills. I heard something about an apartment complex and a dude with corn rows though. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0570.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0570&#34;&gt; To prove our true hipstership, we spent a couple days in Bisbee, AZ. My cousin was getting married near there, and it&amp;rsquo;s where my dad grew up so we jumped on the opportunity to take the tour from a local. First we stopped in Tombstone, which is a tourist trap, one which my dads family always made sure to drive on past. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty hokey indeed but hey, they make some delicious Saspirilla over there. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0596.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0596&#34;&gt; Every building in Bisbee is at least half a century old with wood floors and all that. Here&amp;rsquo;s our hotel room at the Canyon Rose, which I highly recommend. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0600.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0600&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0601.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0601&#34;&gt; The town is literally on the border of Mexico. My dad used to play around in the desert here as a kid, and there wasn&amp;rsquo;t this wall thingy there, so they had to make sure they didn&amp;rsquo;t wander too far and end up over the border. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0602.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0602&#34;&gt; We went to an amazing Gelato shop where we watched some cartoons for a bit. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0610.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0610&#34;&gt; And we went antique shopping. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0611.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0611&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0025.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0025&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_3825.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3825&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_3827.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3827&#34;&gt; Damn it feels good to be a hipster &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_3832.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3832&#34;&gt; Bisbee reminds me a bit of San Fransisco. There&amp;rsquo;s lots of weirdos everywhere and there roads are narrow and scary, and everything is old. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_3833.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3833&#34;&gt; Here&amp;rsquo;s the mine where my Grandpa worked, which shut down in the 70&amp;rsquo;s. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_3838.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3838&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_3840.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3840&#34;&gt; And we saw a bunch of dust devils. How cliche, Arizona. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_3824.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3824&#34;&gt; You know, this is a good metaphor for life. Sometimes you can see something cool in the far off distance but right of front of you is a bunch of bug splatters. We should remember to focus on the cool view in the distance. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_3856.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3856&#34;&gt; Oh yeah we went to Weird Al concert. He played a bunch of his original songs (yes he has a lot of original songs). This is my view. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_3797.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3797&#34;&gt; This is Emily&amp;rsquo;s view. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_3796.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3796&#34;&gt;   Oh look, we went to some other show. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_3789.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3789&#34;&gt;   Ok bye                                 &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/06/img_0512.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0512&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>March 2018 - Baptisms and blowouts</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/march-2018-baptisms-and-blowouts/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Last month I left you on a nasty cliffhanger regarding Emily&amp;rsquo;s job. The past several years Emily has worked 3 different places in an office administrative assistant role. Realizing that administrative assistance isn&amp;rsquo;t her life&amp;rsquo;s work prompted her to start learning web design. I was working on a project to help us as a household manage our recipes and grocery lists, and I recruited her to make it look and feel nice and pretty.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Vacations and Vocations (January and February 2018)</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/vacations-and-vocations-january-and-february-2018/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 01:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Emily went to Oregon and Watched a few basketball games&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_3167.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3167&#34;&gt; Visited a huge bookstore (Powell&amp;rsquo;s books)&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_3084.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3084&#34;&gt; Had some amazing ice cream (you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t think Pear &amp;amp; Blue Cheese ice cream would be any good, but you&amp;rsquo;d be wrong).&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_3681.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3681&#34;&gt; Of course, played some games.&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_5357.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_5357&#34;&gt; And more&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_6061.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_6061&#34;&gt; She had a marvelous time with her mom, sister and extended family and came home tempted to move up to Oregon since we don&amp;rsquo;t move nearly enough already. Speaking of moving, this dog has the right idea.&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_0362.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0362&#34;&gt; In my last update, I told the story of my turning down a job opportunity at a company helping out the lovely, enchanting porn industry. In this episode of dubious job opportunities, I met with some dudes probably somewhere around my age in a fancy office in Scottsdale, and they told me tells of riches and a new cryptocurrency. Basically they&amp;rsquo;re a marketing company wanting to create their own cryptocurrency and use their marketing department to advertise it and make millions or something. My job would be to create simple advertising webpages and essentially copy bitcoin&amp;rsquo;s open source code, with the promise of 1% of the &amp;ldquo;mine&amp;rdquo; in addition to the 70k salary. Honestly, I seriously considered it, not because I&amp;rsquo;m particularly interested in get-rich-quick-schemes, but it&amp;rsquo;s more that I&amp;rsquo;m starved for something interesting to do. I&amp;rsquo;m not afraid to get another job if and/or when the gravy train stops or more likely, I find out there&amp;rsquo;s no gravy in the first place. I had my finger on the trigger and was about to accept the job, but I just felt sick. Was it cowardice, or was it rational thinking and prudence finally kicking in? I do know I wasn&amp;rsquo;t very thrilled with working in an environment where people seem to only care about money. I&amp;rsquo;ll never know what would have happened. I just hope this wasn&amp;rsquo;t my only chance to throw caution to the wind and actually do something interesting.  Or maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll have safe, boring jobs for the rest of my life. First World Problems, amirite? God Bless America. Have some pictures with no context: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_2693.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_0368.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0368&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_3995.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;                                           &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_1342.jpg?w=702&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_0396.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_2214.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_1261.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;   &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_6870.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt; Emily did some charity work and gave an ice cream code to the local homeless guy. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_2313.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt; Oh, our stake received a surprise visit from Jeffrey R Holland, who had come down for a funeral during his weekend that he had off. There is a mission president in our stake who had a daughter in her 30&amp;rsquo;s who unexpectedly passed away and left behind a husband and children. His main message, at least what I got out of it, was words of encouragement for those going through difficult times, in the eloquent, powerful way that is unique to Jeffrey R Holland. Well, I even hate to bring it up, but we moved. Again. We hired movers because we&amp;rsquo;re tired of moving things. We found a nice three bedroom house to rent in Phoenix, and that means that we can finally get a dog!! Also, we kind of live in the ghetto. It&amp;rsquo;s interesting over in our part of the world. But hey, we live close to this place where the rawk happens: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_0390.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt; (featured, Dead To Me with lots of excited yelling people) Also I saw US Bombs. The US Bombs are fronted by a former pro skater who now hobbles around with a cane. If anyone has seen The Other F Word (highly recommended documentary about rockers coping with the responsibilities of fatherhood), he was the one who told the story of his son being hit by a car. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/u-s-bombs_seattle2017_-_by_olga_aguilar.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt; (not actual footage because I usually try and actually watch the show in real life instead of through a glowing rectangular screen) Emily has some interesting news about a web design job offer but I can&amp;rsquo;t tell you any more details because it&amp;rsquo;s the wrong month for the blog post. I can tell you she&amp;rsquo;s now doing a little bit of freelancing though. I think she might be interested in doing more freelancing, though I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to say that. Here are some weird pictures of Emily.                       &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_0401.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;                         &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_0400.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;                 &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_0361.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0361&#34;&gt;                               And here&amp;rsquo;s a weird picture of her foot. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_0370.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0370&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Sojourns and Celebrations: November-December 2017</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/sojourns-and-celebrations-november-december-2017/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 23:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m sure you noticed that I haven&amp;rsquo;t written in a couple months, and I&amp;rsquo;m so sorry. I&amp;rsquo;m so sorry to ruin 2017 for you! If you can&amp;rsquo;t function at full capacity I totally understand. Boy howdy, what an eventful couple of months. Sit back, your feet up, and let me tell you all about it. First, Emily quit her job because, well, it&amp;rsquo;s quite the story so you should ask her if you&amp;rsquo;re dying to know.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>October 2017 - Pinners and Prescott</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/october-2017-pinners-and-prescott/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 02:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;One time we decided to spend an entire Saturday in a magical far away land called Prescott, because it seems like a mysterious mystical town tucked away somewhere in the Arizona desert, and also we&amp;rsquo;re looking for places to live that&amp;rsquo;s not in the center of a giant metropolitan.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Saxaphones and Stravinsky - September 2017</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/saxaphones-and-stravinsky-september-2017/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 22:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re sick of doing the same things over and over, so this month we tried something a little different. This month, we played board games and went to music things!!!!11 There&amp;rsquo;s this little band called the Melvins. Never heard of the Melvins? But you&amp;rsquo;ve heard of Nirvana I&amp;rsquo;m sure. Nirvana wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have existed without the Melvins. These guys are legends. Legends who happen to play smallish clubs, including the Crescent Ballroom in downtown Phoenix. One of the reasons I absolutely needed to see them live was to see King Buzzo&amp;rsquo;s hair in all it&amp;rsquo;s magnificent glory.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>August 2017 - Cars and Concerts</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/august-2017-cars-and-concerts/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 22:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Primus show! If you don&amp;rsquo;t know who Primus is, think of an eclectic mix of Rock N Roll, Larry Graham-esque slap bass, and Willy Wonka. It&amp;rsquo;s truly a beautiful thing. If you don&amp;rsquo;t like Primus then, up yours, you silly non-freak person. I met up my buddy Colton who I haven&amp;rsquo;t hung out with in literally 10 years. He&amp;rsquo;s been into Primus as far back as I can remember, but I&amp;rsquo;m ashamed to say I never got into them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>July 2017 - Foods and Freaks</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/july-2017-foods-and-freaks/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 22:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Our A/C went out and the apartment complex we live in paid for us to stay in a hotel. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_0218.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0218&#34;&gt; We traveled to California and ate food next to dangerous chemicals &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_1337.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_1337&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_5740.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_5740&#34;&gt; Eat up! &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_3056.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3056&#34;&gt; And then ate food next to a safe lake. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_9257.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_9257&#34;&gt; And then ate food and was informed of good things to come. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_4612.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_4612&#34;&gt; Flags representing missions where children and grandchildren have served. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_2448.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_2448&#34;&gt; Ya know, if the state of California were a little more friendly to things like freedom, I might want to move there. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_3634.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3634&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_7434.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_7434&#34;&gt; Continuing on the food theme&amp;hellip; Chick-Fil-A serves you caca, try some Raising Canes instead! &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_3796.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3796&#34;&gt; Oh yeeeeah &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_5509.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_5509&#34;&gt; Ssssh don&amp;rsquo;t tell anybody. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_6483.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_6483&#34;&gt; Num num num num num &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_3117.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3117&#34;&gt; We are going to be fat. Graeters ice cream is one of the clients that I&amp;rsquo;ve been working with for the past year. I discovered they distrubute their wares at our local grocery store. It&amp;rsquo;s too expensive though so forget that, I&amp;rsquo;m just going to pose and put it back on the shelf. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_5210.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_5210&#34;&gt; This month we got to see Laura Stevenson for the third time. Doors were supposed to open at 8:00 but here we are past 8:30 with a long line of people. Not sure what that was about. While we were standing in line, one of the guys from one of my favorite bands, Andrew Jackson Jihad came by and played with the kid that you can see with that glow stick (it sounded like he was friends with the dad). We just assumed he was there to watch the Jeff Rosenstock/Laura Stevenson show, since it seems they&amp;rsquo;re all friends and stuff. As it turns out the guys from AJJ were there to play their first show as a band called Wiccan Babysitter. Their roles were reversed - the singer/guitar player was the bass player and the bass player was the singer/guitar player. That was a fun surprise, and I ended up buying a Wiccan Babysitter record. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_6925.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_6925&#34;&gt; And Laura Stevenson was amazing as usual. (and I implore you to check out this song &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X-GMtVxhJd4&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bGxt1h-2XdY&lt;/a&gt; - Am I crazy for thinking she should be bigger than she is? That&amp;rsquo;s not a fat joke. Maybe guitars scare people? I need answers!) &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_6167.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_6167&#34;&gt; And we got to talk to her for a bit after the show. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_7758.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_7758&#34;&gt; When Jeff Rosenstock&amp;rsquo;s band took the stage the place exploded with energy. People were jumping around and going crazy. It was a sight to behold. We were off the side as to avoid getting crushed by the unrestrained enthusiasm. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-IJCPdhazNY&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-IJCPdhazNY&amp;feature=youtu.be&lt;/a&gt; Mountains making you claustrophobic and gross inversion making it hard to get oxygen in your lungs? Move to Arizona, where the sky is big, and the sunsets are large. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_7965.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_7965&#34;&gt; And I had one of those days where you&amp;rsquo;re traveling down the interstate and a building explodes. You know what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/img_9976.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_9976&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>May 2017 - Records and Rat dogs</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/may-2017-records-and-rat-dogs/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 17:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Howdy y&amp;rsquo;all, this past month saw us doing a whole lot of NOTHING. At least from an outsiders perspective. But first I must mention that Emily visited her family in Utah and she met the new little rat dog named Moose. Emily likes dogs in case you didn&amp;rsquo;t know.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>April 2017 - Cacophonies and concerts</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/april-2017/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 16:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We moved &amp;hellip;again. Here&amp;rsquo;s basically why: this is a decibel reading from our old front door. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/img_2530-e1494175390130.png?w=747&#34; alt=&#34;img_2530.png&#34;&gt; I think I have a higher than average sensitivity to noise. Even small noises have always bothered me. It&amp;rsquo;s nice to have the fan on when I&amp;rsquo;m sleeping, but if it makes even the slightest bit of unusual noise, fuh-get-about-it. We lived in a nice Condo, but there was also a lot of variety in noises that you could hear no matter where you were. Whether in the bathroom, in the bedroom, sleeping or pooping, this is what you would hear: RRRRRRRRffffffff&amp;hellip;swoosh swoosh swoosh&amp;hellip;.BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM bllgh blllgggh blllllgggghh swoosh swoosh RRRRR BOOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;sweet silence for 8 seconds&amp;hellip;.VVVRRrooommm&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..schwump schwump schwump schwump..swoosh tuckaTHUCKtuckaTHUCKtucka BOOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM AAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH The nightmare is finally over. We moved to place only a couple minutes away, but my gosh, I am tired of moving. Enough about you, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about us. Emily got her wisdom teeth taken out. It&amp;rsquo;s always very nerve wracking doing anything healthcare related. We essentially roll the dice, and we could end up paying nothing or thousands of dollars, who the hell knows! Luckily this only cost us less than 200 dollars, and now I know what Emily is like as a druggie: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/img_0518.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0518&#34;&gt; Cats suck &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/img_2375.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_2375&#34;&gt; Even foxes are better &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/img_5124.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_5124&#34;&gt; Emily went on splits with the missionaries and got to do some street contacting! Missions are really easy. I recently found this letter from my mission, which provided some beautiful, beautiful, reminiscences: &lt;a href=&#34;https://dallincoons.wordpress.com/2017/04/16/oakland-mission-chronicles-a-day-in-the-life/&#34;&gt;https://dallincoons.wordpress.com/2017/04/16/oakland-mission-chronicles-a-day-in-the-life/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/img_2535.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_2535&#34;&gt; One solution I&amp;rsquo;ve been exploring to the noise problem is to try and go deaf! So that&amp;rsquo;s why I attended a couple of shows this month. First off Teenage Bottlerocket. The best Ramones-core band out there! People were jumping around going crazy, and it was a fun time. The drummer recently passed away, and he was the brother of the guitar player featured prominently in the image below. This was the first time they&amp;rsquo;ve visited AZ since that time, and you can tell that the band is still grieving but at the same time playing shows seems to be therapeutic. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/img_6778.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_6778&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/img_2634.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_2634&#34;&gt; And everyone knows that ska-punk sucks. But real ska is awesome!!! I went and saw The Slackers, who are definitely better than the Beatles. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve ever been to a real ska show before. It was different. No mosh pits, no stage diving. Just a lot of dancing. It was really fun! &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/18238802_10156493455033868_3814646697594666655_o.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;18238802_10156493455033868_3814646697594666655_o&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/18194645_689315077923157_3728725346335779100_n.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;18194645_689315077923157_3728725346335779100_n&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/18157881_689315181256480_8430796006043334604_n.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;18157881_689315181256480_8430796006043334604_n&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/18157132_689314994589832_6404407049579506252_n.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;18157132_689314994589832_6404407049579506252_n&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/18155777_10156493456468868_8153906891041766448_o.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;18155777_10156493456468868_8153906891041766448_o&#34;&gt;                               &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/img_2537.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_2537&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Oakland Mission chronicles - a day in the life</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/oakland-mission-chronicles-a-day-in-the-life/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 21:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently came across this mission letter I wrote toward the end of my mission and consists of some fairly mundane details, however, I thought it was a good demonstration of a day in the life in the mission - or at least my mission. I share this partially because it&amp;rsquo;s an amusing retrospective but also because I want to add a bit of realism to the naively romanticized idea what missionary work is like that most prospective missionaries have, including myself once upon a time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>March 2017 - Symphonies and Smooches</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/march-2017-symphonies-and-smooches/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 22:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Looks who&amp;rsquo;s back! Did you miss us? You know, I&amp;rsquo;m terrified of becoming a boring, old, low-energy 9-5 commuter who no longer finds child-like joy in the world. That&amp;rsquo;s partially what the blog is for. It&amp;rsquo;s one of the tools in my toolset to help keep the adventure alive. I&amp;rsquo;ve consistently written a blog every month for the past few years. One of the qualities that I like about myself is that I generally have a lot of self-integrity: when I decide to do something, I do it. If I decide I&amp;rsquo;m going to go to the gym every day, I go to the freaking gym every day. When I decide I&amp;rsquo;m going to write a blog every month, that&amp;rsquo;s what I do.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>End of a Year - December 2016</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/end-of-a-year-december-2016/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 23:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We travelled to Rexburg for my sister Janae and her husband Mark&amp;rsquo;s graduation from BYU-Idaho. It was good that we went there in the winter time because we didn&amp;rsquo;t feel as nostalgic as we were worried we might be. We&amp;rsquo;re happy living somewhere warm, thank you very much.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>November 2016 - freaks and farewells</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/november-2016/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 04:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Google thought they would be clever and look for things related to &amp;ldquo;Christmas Party&amp;rdquo; and associate an image with it. Silly Google. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_20031.png&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_2003.PNG&#34;&gt; We played Sheriff of Nottingham, which may or may not involve smuggling contraband. This guy is definitely shady. All you have to do is look at him to know that. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/smuggler.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;smuggler&#34;&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m not like that other guy - there&amp;rsquo;s absolutely no contraband here. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_2001.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_2001&#34;&gt; Emily as the &amp;ldquo;sunbeam whisperer&amp;rdquo;: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_0357.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_0357&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_0362.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_0362&#34;&gt; My sister Janae and her husband Mark flew down from Rexburg for Thanksgiving. We then travelled out to the middle-of-nowhere in the deserts of Southern Arizona for Thanksgiving, where we hung out on a pseudo farm thing, ate food and played with dogs. Have I mentioned that dogs are Emily&amp;rsquo;s favourite thing ever? &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_0380.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_0380&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_0382-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_0382-1&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_0385.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_0385&#34;&gt; That golden retriever likes to, well, retrieve things. We played a game with her by throwing a ball on the roof and she would have to anticipate where it would come down. Well, this one time, I threw the ball very poorly and it got stuck on the roof. Luckily, my brother-in-law, Mark, volunteered to get stuck up on the roof and I generously assisted. You can see the fiasco he created as people scrambled to set up the ladder. Good job, Mark, you almost ruined Thanksgiving! &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_1992.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_1992&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_1993.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_1993&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_1994.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_1994&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/creepy.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;creepy&#34;&gt; Look at these jokers.They look like this pretty much all the time. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_0387.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_0387&#34;&gt; Emily and I have always dreamed of starting a business. So we&amp;rsquo;re creating a product. Boom. It&amp;rsquo;s called PepperRodeo. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_0388.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_0388&#34;&gt; Feast your eyes on the beautiful login page. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/pepperrodeologin.png&#34; alt=&#34;pepperrodeologin&#34;&gt; Punk rock is generally accepted to have more or less started around 1977 with the arrival of bands like the Ramones, The Clash, and the Sex Pistols. Bad Religion formed not soon after in 1979. They made a name for themselves with prominent three-part vocal harmonies, really good guitar playing, and perhaps most defining: intellectually intriguing subject matter. &amp;ldquo;We write songs about what separates man from the animals? Is there a free will? Is there an immortal soul? What&amp;rsquo;s the purpose of a government?&amp;rdquo; Singer and founding member, Greg Graffin is an Anthropology professor at UCLA and Cornell University when he&amp;rsquo;s not gigging with Bad Religion. They seem to see themselves almost as a continuation of philosophers such as Socrates, or I don&amp;rsquo;t know&amp;hellip;umm Kant or something (Don&amp;rsquo;t judge me, you people who know philosophy really well). &amp;ldquo;The pleasure in life is continuing to look for an answer, even though we recognize if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have an answer because it&amp;rsquo;s actually part of human history since time immemorial that these questions have been asked and it&amp;rsquo;s our duty to provoke them and to provoke people to think about them.&amp;rdquo; 35 years later, they&amp;rsquo;re playing Tempe and I&amp;rsquo;m quite interested. Emily came along for the ride. She&amp;rsquo;s probably not as obsessed with the genre as I am, but she &amp;ldquo;gets it&amp;rdquo;. We parked in some random parking lot, hoped we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get towed, and walked the 15-minute trek to the venue, across this lovely bridge: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_1949.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_1949&#34;&gt;. Against Me! was opening, which is a very cool band I&amp;rsquo;m a fan of. And wow, the singer is transexual, check out how hip, cool, and inclusive I am! &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_1951.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_1951&#34;&gt; The punkest punk rocker I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_1957.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_1957&#34;&gt; Hiding from the authorities &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_1958.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_1958&#34;&gt; I thought punk was dead, but look at all these freaks! &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_1959.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_1959&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_1960.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_1960&#34;&gt; They&amp;rsquo;re starting to show their age, but man can they still rock. It was a fun, fun, show.   We had a farewell dinner with our friend the Gill&amp;rsquo;s. We met them in our first church ward when we first moved to Arizona, and we&amp;rsquo;ve been like two peas in a pod ever since. And now they&amp;rsquo;ve moved to Illinois so they&amp;rsquo;re dead to us! Just kidding. Here&amp;rsquo;s our last supper at this cool outdoor restaurant thingy: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_1970.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_1970&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_1972.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_1972&#34;&gt; We miss our homies. That&amp;rsquo;s all folks. Sorry if you were expecting more but there&amp;rsquo;s no refunds and I&amp;rsquo;m calling security.                         &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/12/img_1966.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img_1966&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>October 2016 - Prunes and Parenting</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/october-2016-prunes-and-parenting/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 23:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Emily and I attended a band that we&amp;rsquo;re both fans of - The Dirty Nil. This young band is the glorious mixture of Classic Rock and Punk Rock. In fact, the main front man, Luke Bentham has a tradition of taking the stage wearing a star-smattered shirt in homage to MC5. These fellas know how to put on a great show.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>September 2016 - Bears and Buffalo</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/september-2016-bears-and-buffalo/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 18:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;One normal, average morning Emily went outside to find&amp;hellip;all the cars missing in the parking lot? Did somebody still everybody&amp;rsquo;s cars? Nope. The pavement needed a manicure and so someone towed every car to the other side of the building without warning us(!). I&amp;rsquo;m far more amazed, even impressed, that someone actually did this than I am put off by the confusion and slight inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>August 2016 - Cowboys and Cake</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/august-2016-cowboys-and-cake/</link>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 00:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, well, well. Fancy seeing you here. Come on in and I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you all about our comings and goings. Have a seat. Allow me to be introspective for a moment. This was my first month of working remotely. The people I&amp;rsquo;m working with are &amp;ldquo;A players&amp;rdquo;, which is simultaneously very good and very stressful because I also have to put forth my best effort, and I often feel like an idiot. But you know what? This is exactly the kind of environment I want to be in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>July 2016 - Burgers and Beaches</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/july-2016/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2016 23:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We kicked off July with trip to Huntington Beach California, which is where Emily&amp;rsquo;s grandparents are from. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_0220.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0220&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_0257.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0257&#34;&gt; Despite the fact that we were at a beach, which is supposed to be always warm and sunny, it was cold and windy. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_0235.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0235&#34;&gt; Some took drastic measures: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_0259.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0259&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/08/img_0933.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0933&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_1001.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_1001&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_0215.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0215&#34;&gt; There were certain people we didn&amp;rsquo;t really care much for&amp;hellip;so we buried them. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/08/img_0906.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0906&#34;&gt; And we forced people at gunpoint to play games: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/08/img_0619.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0619&#34;&gt; And of course, we partook of the Holy Burger. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_0264.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0264&#34;&gt; I want to make a pilgrimage to every In-N-Out in existence. Only partially kidding. Several weeks later, we went to my hometown of Lakeside which is by Show Low, or Snowflake maybe  you&amp;rsquo;ve heard of it there&amp;rsquo;s a temple there yes it&amp;rsquo;s sort of by Flagstaff I mean it&amp;rsquo;s on the same side of the state at least&amp;hellip; Here&amp;rsquo;s where Lakeside is: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/08/lakesidelocation.png&#34; alt=&#34;lakesidelocation&#34;&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s located right at that bulb syringe. Let&amp;rsquo;s zoom in and take a closer look, shall we? &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_0271.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0271&#34;&gt;. There&amp;rsquo;s all kinds of stuff to do in Lakeside. Like farmers markets. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_0268.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0268&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_0269.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0269&#34;&gt; You can take hipster photographs. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_1111.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_1111&#34;&gt; And there&amp;rsquo;s tons of scenic hikes &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_1091.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_1091&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_1092.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_1092&#34;&gt; The original goal was to go camping. I soon realized that: a) there was a huge fire that almost burned down the whole town, so no campfires were allowed except in designated camping spots. b) you have to pay to camp at designated camping areas. c) I&amp;rsquo;m not about to pay money for something that is outrageously abundant (although I do pay for bottled water sometimes so it must not bother me that much). Thus we decided to camp in my parents backyard: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_1119.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_1119&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_1125.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_1125&#34;&gt; Emily woke up to the sound of a hummingbird doing hummingbird things: [youtube &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l-y9&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l-y9&lt;/a&gt;_W1kwCs] It was a great time. I like small towns, ya know? My sister Janae, and her husband Mark &amp;ldquo;some guy&amp;rdquo; Johnson, came for a visit. You can check out her &lt;a href=&#34;https://ourjohnsonadventures.wordpress.com/2016/08/02/july-update/&#34;&gt;side of the story&lt;/a&gt;, but I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you how things really went down. We went to Golden Coral. It really isn&amp;rsquo;t the best food in the world, but it has cotton candy and cute kids. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_1404.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_1404&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_1402.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_1402&#34;&gt; We went to a place called Bookmans that is a playground for nerds. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_1437.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_1437&#34;&gt; We bought Decline and Fall of the Roman Empire, Ender&amp;rsquo;s Game and the next books in the series: Speaker of the Dead and Xenocide. We also bought the unabridged Les Miserables because we&amp;rsquo;re HARDCORE. And we bought some Harry Potter books (because we&amp;rsquo;re&amp;hellip;hardcore?). Reading is frickin&amp;rsquo; cool. Look at these people: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_1439.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_1439&#34;&gt; We played some crazy games of Cosmic Encounter, in which people are wheelin&amp;rsquo; and dealin&amp;rsquo; and you can totally trust me, I have your best interest at heart! &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_1422.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_1422&#34;&gt; This is a crazy, crazy, game. I can&amp;rsquo;t repeat the things that I&amp;rsquo;ve seen and heard. Well, I finally pulled the trigger (so to speak) and quit my job. Now I will be working from home with a company that uses Laravel&amp;hellip;..the best way I can describe it is I&amp;rsquo;m now able to work with something that is like the Apple product of the PHP programming world. It&amp;rsquo;s sleek, elegant, and generally a joy to work with. I could hardly of asked for anything better. WEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE                                                   &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_1420.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_1420&#34;&gt;   *The reason the town next to Lakeside is called Show Low is because two guys who were equal partners in a 100,000 acre ranch decided there wasn&amp;rsquo;t room enough for both of them (!) and so they played a game of poker to determine who would get the ranch. During a rousing night of poker, Marion Clark said &amp;ldquo;If you can show low, win&amp;rdquo;.  Corydon Cooley turned up the deuce of clubs and that was that. He named the settlement Show Low and the main street became the &amp;ldquo;Deuce of Clubs&amp;rdquo;. Now you know. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2016/07/img_1045.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_1045&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Holidays and HurracUHNns - June 2016</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/holidays-and-hurracuhnns-june-2016/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 02:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve been working on the design phase of a recipe and grocery list web app named Pepper Rodeo that we are building. We&amp;rsquo;ve determined that we want to spend 90 percent of our time designing it and so when it comes time to code it, you can bang out the code in no time flat. That&amp;rsquo;s something I learned at college. See? Sometimes college isn&amp;rsquo;t always a waste of time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>May 2016 - Pirates and midgets</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/may-2016-pirates-and-midgets/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 02:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Well we moved to a new place YET AGAIN. Why? Cause we get bored, that&amp;rsquo;s why. And I wanted to be closer to work I guess. Yes we successfully moved to Tempe, which is the city next door to Phoenix. Tempe is a poop dump. Well not really, but there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of college students. That&amp;rsquo;s it, I&amp;rsquo;m flossing. I had to go to the dentist to get some teeth filled. My mom&amp;rsquo;s enamel sucks and seems like I inherited it. Going to the dentist isn&amp;rsquo;t bad except when you have to hold your mouth open for an hour straight while you periodically get waterboarded.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                
            
        
    </channel>
</rss>
