<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Uncategorized on Site Title</title>
        <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/tags/uncategorized/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Site Title</description>

         
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>End of Summer</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/end-of-summer-comments/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 19:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>- Oct 6, 2023
That’s so cool that Emily is taking a dance class. Loved the video! Also, Ninja Warrior looks intense but fun. I love that Calvin and Karis get to go to preschool together.—Shauni
Very cool Dallin. Thanks for sharing!</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>End of Summer</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/end-of-summer/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 19:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Emily has been attending dance class and has been working on a performance inspired by the Barbie movie. Watch the video here and see if you can spot her:
https://www.youtube.com/embed/JYefhluzI5o?si=hFCzdrd3jVehkN7W
I&rsquo;ve been going to Ninja Warrior class that Mark introduced me to which has been a fun (and challenging) way to stay in shape. I was quite bad at it at first but have improved drastically since I started attending which has been rewarding.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>More June 2023</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/more-june-2023/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 18:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>What&rsquo;s nifty about where we live is that a berry farm is right down the road where can go pick fresh blueberries and blackberries, but 20 minutes away is a big-ish city.
We&rsquo;re not the best gardeners (yet), but we recently harvested the first thing we&rsquo;ve successfully grown. Calvin was pretty excited about that.
We went to a little amusement park about 40 minutes away that is geared toward kids Calvin&rsquo;s age.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>November 2022 - June 2023</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/november-2022-june-2023/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 23:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>In November we travelled to visit Owasso, Oklahoma to visit Janae and go house viewing. Calvin got to play with his cousins and we got a reprieve from the bitter Rexburg winter. The fact that we could actually go outside for more than 5 minutes without cursing our very existence was a good sign (also with the way the housing market was going in Idaho, pay a premium for the priveledge).</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>(If) I Went On a Mushroom Trip</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/if-i-went-on-a-mushroom-trip-comments/</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 03:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Melanie Coons - Jun 6, 2023
You’re such a creative, insightful writer!
I like the cut of your jib, and would like to cavort with you about my own experience soon
Some excellent insights here Dallin. Thanks for sharing!
So many beautiful insights! And the fact that there’s even more than what you shared is amazing. I got a little teary reading about you getting teary 🥹🥹</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>(If) I Went On a Mushroom Trip</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/if-i-went-on-a-mushroom-trip/</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 03:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>I, seeking greater enlightenment, embarked on a journey.
I had a guide with me who was there to be there with me to help me through the experience and who was able to write my thoughts and insights as I verbally expressed them. My trip was not what I was expecting. I was anticipating that I would put on my headphones and experience music on an entirely new level.
Instead, I experienced trees.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>August - October 2022</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/august-october-2022/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 18:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>We&rsquo;ve built up quite a montage of Calvin playing with cars and trucks and digging in dirt. I think we&rsquo;ve identified his favorite activity, and one of our favorite activities is taking redundant pictures of his cuteness. He also humors us and goes on hikes (eh, more like nature walks), but maybe that&rsquo;s because he knows we always have some trucks stashed away to play with. On our walks, we often stumble upon highly diggable dirt and those come in handy.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Summer 2022</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/summer-2022-2/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 03:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Kev&rsquo;s been spending a lot of time doing what he loves to do most.
play with cars play with trucks look at cars look at trucks request that we talk about cars and trucks We had one last hurrah with Jane and Mark&rsquo;s family before they headed off to Oklahoma. We tried to &lsquo;hold down the fort&rsquo; with the kids while they had a yard sale, and then went out for ice cream.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Summer 2022</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/summer-2022/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Kev&rsquo;s been spending a lot of time doing what he loves to do most.
play with cars play with trucks look at cars look at trucks request that we talk about cars and trucks We had one last hurrah with Jane and Mark&rsquo;s family before they headed off to Oklahoma. We tried to &lsquo;hold down the fort&rsquo; with the kids while they had a yard sale, and then went out for ice cream.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Calvin</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/calvin/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 19:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>This might seem like it&rsquo;s coming out of the blue but we&rsquo;re changing Kevin&rsquo;s name to Calvin. We&rsquo;ve been thinking about this since almost the day he was born.
When we were picking a name during pregnancy for the life of us we couldn&rsquo;t decide on a name for a boy that we liked. Ramone was our favorite, but we were reluctant to use what traditionally is a Hispanic name as his first name.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>A Dude Named Dallin</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/a-dude-named-dallin/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 19:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Hobbies
I’ve loved collecting vinyl, much of it from criminally obscure bands who only pressed 300 copies of a record in 2014 or whatever. A part of me thinks of record collecting as ‘archiving’. You might ask why I collect vinyl if I can hear the music on the internet. Or you might not ask, in which case I will give the answers unsolicited.
Vinyl sounds better than the compressed digital counterpart sent via electrical pulses through wires.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>A Boy Named Kev</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/a-boy-named-kev/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 20:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Kev is still learning to talk and the words he uses don&rsquo;t sound like the words we use, but we&rsquo;ve learned to pick up on which of his sounds equates to words we use. Here&rsquo;s a sampling of sounds and their associated words:
Bwow! - (probably his favorite word) means truck, car, or any kind of vehicle with wheels really.
Me! - help me!
Ball - ball
Eh - egg</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Why I Don&#39;t Want To Go To Church</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/why-i-dont-want-to-go-to-church-comments/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 02:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Chris Davis - Aug 1, 2021
Well and bravely stated Dallin. I understand where you are coming from and continue to be proud to have you as a son in law. I do believe in a just god with infinite love and compassion, although I don&rsquo;t always understand why so much pain exist in this world. That said, I&rsquo;m confident in a continuation after this life and that we&rsquo;ll remember, and be able to build on, the relationships we&rsquo;ve fostered.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Why I Don&#39;t Want To Go To Church</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/why-i-dont-want-to-go-to-church/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 02:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>I was baptized a member of The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints when I was 8 years old, which is the Catholic equivalent of being baptized as an infant, and I have been a faithful member for most of my life since then. The LDS church is not just a church to attend on Sunday. It’s a lifestyle that governs many, if not most, aspects of one&rsquo;s life. All of my major life decisions have been influenced by my belief in the teachings of the church.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>January 2021 Deserts and Development</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/january-2021-deserts-and-development/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 02:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>January has historically been the toughest month of the year, at least the years where we&rsquo;ve lived somewhere cold. The thrill of Christmas has gone the way of the carbonation in a flat, half-finished can of coke and the road to spring looks arduous and cold. Emily might seem nice and all, but as long as I&rsquo;ve known her she has had a deep, abiding hatred in her heart for snow.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Beware the Moral Monopoly</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/beware-the-moral-monopoly/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 21:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>There is the way life works and there is the way I wish life worked. This is how I wish it worked: if you have good intentions, you are guaranteed to make good decisions. However, it doesn&rsquo;t take much imagination to produce scenarios where this isn&rsquo;t the case. For example, I may have good intentions to fix my friend&rsquo;s car, but unless I&rsquo;ve gained knowledge in car mechanics somewhere along the way, I may actually do more harm than good.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>The End of a Year, 2020 edition</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/the-end-of-a-year-2020-edition-comments/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 18:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Chris Davis - Dec 0, 2020
Great update Dallin! I certainly need to read more&hellip; the “fast food” social media time has cut into my real reading time more than I like to admit.
I suspect it&rsquo;s not just you :) Reading books is great, but takes extra discipline these days. We really got back into the habit of reading with the Kindle app, and now we each own our own Kindle.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>The End of a Year, 2020 edition</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/the-end-of-a-year-2020-edition/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 18:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Several months ago I wrote about my job search, and some of the failures along the way. In September, I was brought on board to SpotOn as a software engineer, using a language called Go. This is a language I&rsquo;m new to but is one that I was very interested in gaining more experience in. At least 6 months before I started this job I read a book about Go and started solving programming puzzles through a website called exercism.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Trepidations of a Parent, One Year later</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/trepidations-of-a-parent-one-year-later-comments/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 22:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Chris Davis - Dec 2, 2020
Good insights Dallin. Thanks for sharing them and your growing family with us. Love you guys! Chris &amp; Annette</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Trepidations of a Parent, One Year later</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/trepidations-of-a-parent-one-year-later/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 22:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>There&rsquo;s a common type of social media post, most typically from parents of small children. You know the ones. Parents are overflowing with gratitude and positivity. I have no reason to doubt the authenticity of such posts. However, I don&rsquo;t believe they adequately capture the full spectrum of the wellspring of emotion that comes with being a parent.
I&rsquo;m a parent (as of one year ago) so I can say with some first-hand knowledge that sometimes you do feel an extra measure of gratitude and joy, but more often life just as glamorous and romantic as it usually isn&rsquo;t.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Boundaries</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/boundaries/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 03:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Boundaries, a book by Henry Cloud and John Townsend, makes me wonder what percentage of human malcontent is a direct result of some level of inappropriate boundaries. The subject of boundaries is a meaty one as I&rsquo;ve discovered, but I will sample a few specifics of what I found to be the most thought-provoking ideas:
Having appropriate boundaries in our lives means having the discernment to know when to say &rsquo;no&rsquo; and when to say &lsquo;yes&rsquo;, which is fundamental to healthy, fulfilling, and mutually beneficial relationships.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Hurric-uns and hiatuses</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/hurric-uns-and-hiatuses/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 20:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>In August we traveled to Hurric-un (it&rsquo;s a hick Utah pronunciation - just go with it) for the annual family vacation on Emily&rsquo;s side.
To kick things off right, we did the nerdiest thing you could possibly do other than larping. Dungeons and Dragons, which all we all know, is Satan&rsquo;s game. This is what it looks like to be sucked into the occult.
I think we won the game.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Kitten Forever</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/kitten-forever-comments/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Mom - Aug 6, 2020
I love your writing style. You make me laugh out loud. Keep it up! 👍🏻❤️❤️❤️</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Kitten Forever</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/kitten-forever/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 22:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Emily and I have a lot of overlap in our music tastes. While I have more of a tendency to roam into the heavier music, and I seem to have a greater affinity for ska and reggae than she does, we both enjoy much of the same things. One of the bands that we both love is a band called Screaming Females.
Screaming Females is a great band name, but a bit of a misnomer.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Fun With Failure</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/fun-with-failure-comments/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Chris - Aug 1, 2020
Give it a few more months. Post vaccine, we should see a decent rebound. Mid-market cities (not just Salt Lake 😉) are worth exploring, but it’s probably slim pickings until economic conditions start to improve. That said, you are in one of the best fields once that turn around comes.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Fun With Failure</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/fun-with-failure/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>It&rsquo;s a fantastic time to try and find a new job, and so I&rsquo;m taking full advantage of these flourishing economic times. It certainly helps that I&rsquo;m trying to switch to a new programming language and I&rsquo;m going for a bit of a salary increase.
I&rsquo;ve been doing a lot of interviewing lately, and it&rsquo;s been interesting to see the different interview styles. Software engineering interviews are always different but still have some common characteristics.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Kev and Kin</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/kev-and-kin/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 16:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>We started feeding Kev solid foods, though it doesn&rsquo;t seem like much of it goes to the correct location. Still, it&rsquo;s good for him to practice, and at the very least it seems like he enjoys playing with all the interesting textures.
Here&rsquo;s a video of him trying solid food for the first time. We now let him play with his food, which means he gets really messy and disgusting, and so we make sure to eat dinner right before bath time.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Ambitions and Achievements</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/ambitions-and-achievements-comments/</link>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 04:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Melanie Merrill Coons - Jun 0, 2020
I loved reading your blog! (That last picture is a hoot!!) We&rsquo;re excited to see what your next adventure will be. :)</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Ambitions and Achievements</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/ambitions-and-achievements/</link>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 04:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>I haven&rsquo;t written a proper monthly update since July of 2018, which is almost 2 years ago. Time has been a very limited resource lately, and so I&rsquo;ll make that my official excuse. Yeah, that&rsquo;s it.
I have been feeling the itch to start blogging again, although I&rsquo;m not yet sure exactly what form it will take. The monthly updates are fun, but I also would like to write more &ldquo;big idea&rdquo; kind of stuff, and sometimes I just want to talk about me, which is what most of this post will probably consist of.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Grief and Gratitude Part 2</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/grief-and-gratitude-part-2/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Kev was born on 7:11, Tuesday morning, after a greuling 48-hour marathon. For the remainer of the day, we had visitors and nurses coming to our room every 30 minutes to poke and prod kev, give us advice, give Emily medicine, poke and prod Kev again, check to see how much he poop he ejected out of his bum, repeated ad naseum. Similarly, most of our memory of the subsequent stay in the the hospital is mostly of people checking up on us and giving us food, and even a nurse once offering to take Kev to the nursery at 2 in the morning so we could get an hour or two of sleep.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Grief and Gratitude - Kevin&#39;s birth</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/grief-and-gratitude-kevins-birth/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Our doctor, Dr. Allphin, let us know in one of Emily’s appointments leading up to the due date that he was going to be leaving on vacation for the Thanksgiving holiday. That information coupled with the fact that he didn&rsquo;t want us to go past 41 weeks of pregnancy meant that we might have to make a hard decision. We had never really thought too hard about induction. For some reason, it just didn’t seem like something we needed to worry about or mentally prepare for such a possibility.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>&#34;I&#39;m so excited for you guys&#34; - Trepidations of a soon to be parent</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/im-so-excited-for-you-guys-trepidations-of-a-soon-to-be-parent/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 21:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>People are excited for us to have a child. Are we excited? It depends on how you define excited I suppose. If we stick to the dictionary definition, &ldquo;stirred emotionally; agitated&rdquo;, then yes, I guess we are excited. Are we excited as in &ldquo;I&rsquo;m not happy and fulfilled until x event happens&rdquo;? Absolutely, unequivocally, no. We&rsquo;re comfortable - perhaps a little too comfortable. When we tell people that we&rsquo;re incredibly nervous about parenthood, the response is typically reassurance that we&rsquo;re going to be fine parents.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>An Anecdotal Rock and Roll Affair</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/an-anecdotal-rock-and-roll-affair/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 00:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>I work on a computer all day and I had set a reminder to buy tickets to a band called the Distillers, a punk rock band who were reuniting and playing together for the first time in 14 years. (&ldquo;Fun fact&rdquo;: the frontwoman of the band, Brody Dalle used to be married to Tim Armstrong from Rancid, and whose breakup is immortalized in the Rancid song Tropical London.) Thanks to my timely notification, I hopped on immediately and bought two tickets the exact minute they went on sale, and to my suprise, the show completely sold out approximately 3 minutes after they were first made available.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Adventures and adversity (part two)</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/adventures-and-adversity-part-two/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 02:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>I&rsquo;ve been struggling with motivation for writing these blog posts. One reason I know for sure is due to how busy we&rsquo;ve been this year. I&rsquo;m working full time, as a software engineer remotely while going to school part-time (a little more than part-time actually). I first started writing monthly updates in the form of a blog post sometime in 2014 when we decided to pack up and strike out on our own in the mythical land known as Arizona.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Adversity and Adventure - 2018 second half (part1)</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/adversity-and-adventure-2018-second-half-part1/</link>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 03:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Oh hey, it&rsquo;s been a while! Oh boy, do we have some stories to tell. So what&rsquo;s new with us? Everything. Everything is different. Let&rsquo;s start from the beginning because I always tell people &ldquo;yeah we&rsquo;re in Idaho, it&rsquo;s a long story&rdquo;. Well here&rsquo;s the long story: In February of 2018, we moved from an apartment in Tempe to a rental house in Phoenix. I knew that it was only a matter of time before I quit my job because I was already at that time getting excruciatingly bored.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Mugs and Monsoons - June/July 2018</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/mugs-and-monsoons-june-july-2018/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 22:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>We went to Hurricane for our annual summer vacation with the in-laws, and we had our usual MO of crap tons of board games and quiplash. Oh and this thing almost killed us. Well, not really but the story is that we heard a loud noise, and looked over and saw a dust cloud billowing up from the wall of the yard. We come to find out that a man had lost control of his boat that he was pulling, and it came careening into the sidewalk and almost into the wall, but it missed, nobody was hurt, and it all turned out amazingly well except for some bushes and a flat tire or two.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Hipsters and Hinterlands</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/hipsters-and-hinterlands/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 21:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>We&rsquo;ve turned hipster. I have proof. Look: I will now tell you the story about our search for a plant. We went downtown where there&rsquo;s artsy fartsy murals&hellip; And we bought a plant&hellip; The end. There&rsquo;s a band that mentions Arizona sunsets in their song, probably because they look like this: At some point we went to see Lay Mizz (which is how everyone says it) with my bro and his bro (bro as in friend, except for the first one which is in reference to my brother from the same mother).</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>March 2018 - Baptisms and blowouts</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/march-2018-baptisms-and-blowouts-comments/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Nate dog - Apr 1, 2018
That&rsquo;s awesome emily! Miss you guys!</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>March 2018 - Baptisms and blowouts</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/march-2018-baptisms-and-blowouts/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Last month I left you on a nasty cliffhanger regarding Emily&rsquo;s job. The past several years Emily has worked 3 different places in an office administrative assistant role. Realizing that administrative assistance isn&rsquo;t her life&rsquo;s work prompted her to start learning web design. I was working on a project to help us as a household manage our recipes and grocery lists, and I recruited her to make it look and feel nice and pretty.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Vacations and Vocations (January and February 2018)</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/vacations-and-vocations-january-and-february-2018/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 01:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Emily went to Oregon and Watched a few basketball games Visited a huge bookstore (Powell&rsquo;s books) Had some amazing ice cream (you wouldn&rsquo;t think Pear &amp; Blue Cheese ice cream would be any good, but you&rsquo;d be wrong). Of course, played some games. And more She had a marvelous time with her mom, sister and extended family and came home tempted to move up to Oregon since we don&rsquo;t move nearly enough already.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Sojourns and Celebrations: November-December 2017</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/sojourns-and-celebrations-november-december-2017/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 23:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>I&rsquo;m sure you noticed that I haven&rsquo;t written in a couple months, and I&rsquo;m so sorry. I&rsquo;m so sorry to ruin 2017 for you! If you can&rsquo;t function at full capacity I totally understand. Boy howdy, what an eventful couple of months. Sit back, your feet up, and let me tell you all about it. First, Emily quit her job because, well, it&rsquo;s quite the story so you should ask her if you&rsquo;re dying to know.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>October 2017 - Pinners and Prescott</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/october-2017-pinners-and-prescott/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 02:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>One time we decided to spend an entire Saturday in a magical far away land called Prescott, because it seems like a mysterious mystical town tucked away somewhere in the Arizona desert, and also we&rsquo;re looking for places to live that&rsquo;s not in the center of a giant metropolitan. It was a pretty cool place, and we found some Super Cute Little Houses that probably aren&rsquo;t available because they&rsquo;re too small and cute, but we were still taking notes.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Saxaphones and Stravinsky - September 2017</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/saxaphones-and-stravinsky-september-2017/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 22:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>We&rsquo;re sick of doing the same things over and over, so this month we tried something a little different. This month, we played board games and went to music things!!!!11 There&rsquo;s this little band called the Melvins. Never heard of the Melvins? But you&rsquo;ve heard of Nirvana I&rsquo;m sure. Nirvana wouldn&rsquo;t have existed without the Melvins. These guys are legends. Legends who happen to play smallish clubs, including the Crescent Ballroom in downtown Phoenix.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>August 2017 - Cars and Concerts</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/august-2017-cars-and-concerts/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 22:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Primus show! If you don&rsquo;t know who Primus is, think of an eclectic mix of Rock N Roll, Larry Graham-esque slap bass, and Willy Wonka. It&rsquo;s truly a beautiful thing. If you don&rsquo;t like Primus then, up yours, you silly non-freak person. I met up my buddy Colton who I haven&rsquo;t hung out with in literally 10 years. He&rsquo;s been into Primus as far back as I can remember, but I&rsquo;m ashamed to say I never got into them.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>July 2017 - Foods and Freaks</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/july-2017-foods-and-freaks/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 22:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Our A/C went out and the apartment complex we live in paid for us to stay in a hotel. We traveled to California and ate food next to dangerous chemicals Eat up! And then ate food next to a safe lake. And then ate food and was informed of good things to come. Flags representing missions where children and grandchildren have served. Ya know, if the state of California were a little more friendly to things like freedom, I might want to move there.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>June 2017 - Weddings and Wanderings</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/june-2017-weddings-and-wanderings/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 01:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Check out this photographic essay chronicling our adventures for June 2017 which finds our heroes traveling to Maine to surprise unsuspecting brides, the conquering of the land of Yellowstone, and a cute baby. [youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JjAwR8vp9kY?ecver=1&amp;w=560&amp;h=315]</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>May 2017 - Records and Rat dogs</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/may-2017-records-and-rat-dogs/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 17:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Howdy y&rsquo;all, this past month saw us doing a whole lot of NOTHING. At least from an outsiders perspective. But first I must mention that Emily visited her family in Utah and she met the new little rat dog named Moose. Emily likes dogs in case you didn&rsquo;t know. She also likes llamas Emily works at a company which sells accessories for people who drink wine. One of the new products in their line is a purse in which you can store wine.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>April 2017 - Cacophonies and concerts</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/april-2017/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 16:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>We moved &hellip;again. Here&rsquo;s basically why: this is a decibel reading from our old front door. I think I have a higher than average sensitivity to noise. Even small noises have always bothered me. It&rsquo;s nice to have the fan on when I&rsquo;m sleeping, but if it makes even the slightest bit of unusual noise, fuh-get-about-it. We lived in a nice Condo, but there was also a lot of variety in noises that you could hear no matter where you were.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Oakland Mission chronicles - a day in the life</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/oakland-mission-chronicles-a-day-in-the-life-comments/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 21:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>April 2017 – dallincoons - May 0, 2017
[…] https://dallincoons.wordpress.com/2017/04/16/oakland-mission-chronicles-a-day-in-the-life/ […]</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Oakland Mission chronicles - a day in the life</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/oakland-mission-chronicles-a-day-in-the-life/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 21:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>_I recently came across this mission letter I wrote toward the end of my mission and consists of some fairly mundane details, however, I thought it was a good demonstration of a day in the life in the mission - or at least my mission. I share this partially because it&rsquo;s an amusing retrospective but also because I want to add a bit of realism to the naively romanticized idea what missionary work is like that most prospective missionaries have, including myself once upon a time.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>15 Minutes - The Broadways</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/15-minutes-the-broadways/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 22:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>I drove to my stupid job today, got stopped at an intersection 15 minutes of my life just rolled away I looked at the guy next to me he didn&rsquo;t seem so happy no ones happy but everyone&rsquo;s too busy to see let&rsquo;s go shopping today drive our fancy cars to the fancy malls and for lunch we&rsquo;ll have big macs I wish I could turn the clock back to when I was ten when I wasn&rsquo;t scared of everything and everything wasn&rsquo;t so f****ing crowded and I wonder if my kids will ever see a horizon untouched by billboards and shopping malls and I wonder if this crazy world thinks I&rsquo;m the one who&rsquo;s crazy what if I&rsquo;m the one who&rsquo;s crazy?</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>March 2017 - Symphonies and Smooches</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/march-2017-symphonies-and-smooches/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 22:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Looks who&rsquo;s back! Did you miss us? You know, I&rsquo;m terrified of becoming a boring, old, low-energy 9-5 commuter who no longer finds child-like joy in the world. That&rsquo;s partially what the blog is for. It&rsquo;s one of the tools in my toolset to help keep the adventure alive. I&rsquo;ve consistently written a blog every month for the past few years. One of the qualities that I like about myself is that I generally have a lot of self-integrity: when I decide to do something, I do it.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>End of a Year - December 2016</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/end-of-a-year-december-2016-comments/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 23:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Robert - Jan 1, 2017
Cool! I like the app&hellip; that&rsquo;s all</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>End of a Year - December 2016</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/end-of-a-year-december-2016/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 23:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>We travelled to Rexburg for my sister Janae and her husband Mark&rsquo;s graduation from BYU-Idaho. It was good that we went there in the winter time because we didn&rsquo;t feel as nostalgic as we were worried we might be. We&rsquo;re happy living somewhere warm, thank you very much. In Rexburg, sometimes you have to scrape the inside of the windows. You can&rsquo;t even see their dresses because of the stupid coats.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Top 100 songs 70-61  (2016)</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/top-100-songs-70-61-2016/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 16:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Good Life - Weezer I love the early Weezer songs because of how much honesty and personal history is infused in each song. This song was written after Weezer had a very successful debut album and Rivers Cuomo, the singer and main songwriter, decided being a rock star sucked. He decided instead of being a rockstar, he would attend Harvard. This is part of a batch of songs that were written in the middle of winter in Boston.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Top 100 songs 80-71</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/top-100-songs-80-71/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 14:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Simple Man - Bouncing Souls No this is not a cover of Lynyrd Skynyrd. There&rsquo;s two eras of the Bouncing Souls. The first 5 albums were overflowing of with pure youthful energy and absurdly relatable songs to normal people who are simultaneously excited and scared about life. The latter half of the Bouncing Souls catalog is music from seemingly boring, old, mature dudes. But between those two eras is this album, an album chronicling the feelings of people who are getting older and wiser, but not quite boring and jaded yet.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>I Want to Conquer the World - Bad Religion</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/i-want-to-conquer-the-world-bad-religion/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 12:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Hey Brother Christian with your high and might errand, Your actions speak so loud, I can&rsquo;t hear a word you&rsquo;re saying. Hey Sister Bleeding Heart with all of your compassion, Your labors soothe the hurt but can&rsquo;t assuage temptation. Hey man of science with your perfect rules of measure, Can you improve this place with the data that you gather? Hey Mother Mercy can your loins bear fruit forever? Is your fecundity a trammel or a treasure?</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>November 2016 - freaks and farewells</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/november-2016-comments/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 04:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Robert - Dec 1, 2016
Good blog, good blog.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>November 2016 - freaks and farewells</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/november-2016/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 04:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Google thought they would be clever and look for things related to &ldquo;Christmas Party&rdquo; and associate an image with it. Silly Google. We played Sheriff of Nottingham, which may or may not involve smuggling contraband. This guy is definitely shady. All you have to do is look at him to know that. I&rsquo;m not like that other guy - there&rsquo;s absolutely no contraband here. Emily as the &ldquo;sunbeam whisperer&rdquo;: My sister Janae and her husband Mark flew down from Rexburg for Thanksgiving.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>October 2016 - Prunes and Parenting</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/october-2016-prunes-and-parenting/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 23:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Emily and I attended a band that we&rsquo;re both fans of - The Dirty Nil. This young band is the glorious mixture of Classic Rock and Punk Rock. In fact, the main front man, Luke Bentham has a tradition of taking the stage wearing a star-smattered shirt in homage to MC5. These fellas know how to put on a great show. Luke is one of the most charismatic and entertaining frontman I&rsquo;ve ever seen.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>September 2016 - Bears and Buffalo</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/september-2016-bears-and-buffalo/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 18:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>One normal, average morning Emily went outside to find&hellip;all the cars missing in the parking lot? Did somebody still everybody&rsquo;s cars? Nope. The pavement needed a manicure and so someone towed every car to the other side of the building without warning us(!). I&rsquo;m far more amazed, even impressed, that someone actually did this than I am put off by the confusion and slight inconvenience. Everyone needs a giant teddy bear in their lives.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Top 100 songs: 90-81</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/top-100-songs-90-81/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 03:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Songs 100-91 The Passenger - Iggy Pop We&rsquo;re jumping in the way-back machine for this one: 1977. The legendary Iggy Pop. This is a slower meandering tune. I can visualize myself cruising down the highway underneath the stars. The pacing, the melody, and the lyrics come together to perfectly capture this feeling. I recommend this song to the non-punkers out there. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hLhN__oEHaw Our Own Way - Hot Water Music Ah, we&rsquo;re getting gruffer with this tune.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>August 2016 - Cowboys and Cake</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/august-2016-cowboys-and-cake/</link>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 00:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Well, well, well. Fancy seeing you here. Come on in and I&rsquo;ll tell you all about our comings and goings. Have a seat. Allow me to be introspective for a moment. This was my first month of working remotely. The people I&rsquo;m working with are &ldquo;A players&rdquo;, which is simultaneously very good and very stressful because I also have to put forth my best effort, and I often feel like an idiot.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Top 100 Songs: 100-91</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/top-100-songs-100-91-comments/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 04:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Top 100 songs: 90-81 – dallincoons - Oct 6, 2016
[…] Songs 100-91 […]</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Top 100 Songs: 100-91</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/top-100-songs-100-91/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 04:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Born Free - Bouncing Souls Born Free has a wonderful sense of urgency and purpose. It knows exactly where it&rsquo;s going, it came to deliver a message as fast as possible, in a just a little over a minute. I can&rsquo;t help but think of this as a libertarian anthem. The way that dictators and &ldquo;progressives&rdquo; of all types have always gained power is through playing on fears that come innately as humans.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>July 2016 - Burgers and Beaches</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/july-2016/</link>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2016 23:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>We kicked off July with trip to Huntington Beach California, which is where Emily&rsquo;s grandparents are from. Despite the fact that we were at a beach, which is supposed to supposed to be always warm and sunny, it was cold and windy. Some took drastic measures: There were certain people we didn&rsquo;t really care much for&hellip;so we buried them. And we forced people at gunpoint to play games: And of course, we partook of the Holy Burger.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Holidays and HurracUHNns - June 2016</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/holidays-and-hurracuhnns-june-2016/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 02:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>We&rsquo;ve been working on the design phase of an recipe and grocery list web app named Pepper Rodeo that we are building. We&rsquo;ve determined that we want to spend 90 percent of our time designing it and so when it comes time to code it, you can bang out the code in no time flat. That&rsquo;s something I learned at college. See? Sometimes college isn&rsquo;t always a waste of time. Basically we created as many &ldquo;Use cases&rdquo; and &ldquo;User Stories&rdquo; as we can think of.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>May 2016 - Pirates and midgets</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/may-2016-pirates-and-midgets/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 02:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>Well we moved to a new place YET AGAIN. Why? Cause we get bored, that&rsquo;s why. And I wanted to be closer to work I guess. Yes we successfully moved to Tempe, which is the city next door to Phoenix. Tempe is a poop dump. Well not really, but there&rsquo;s a lot of college students. That&rsquo;s it, I&rsquo;m flossing. I had to go to the dentist to get some teeth filled.</description>
                </item>
                
            
        
    </channel>
</rss>
