<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Image on Devil&#39;s Avocado</title>
        <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/tags/image/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Devil&#39;s Avocado</description>

         
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Vacations and Vocations (January and February 2018)</title>
                    <link>https://family.dallincoons.com/vacations-and-vocations-january-and-february-2018/</link>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 01:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Emily went to Oregon and Watched a few basketball games&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_3167.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3167&#34;&gt; Visited a huge bookstore (Powell&amp;rsquo;s books)&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_3084.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3084&#34;&gt; Had some amazing ice cream (you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t think Pear &amp;amp; Blue Cheese ice cream would be any good, but you&amp;rsquo;d be wrong).&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_3681.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_3681&#34;&gt; Of course, played some games.&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_5357.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_5357&#34;&gt; And more&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_6061.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_6061&#34;&gt; She had a marvelous time with her mom, sister and extended family and came home tempted to move up to Oregon since we don&amp;rsquo;t move nearly enough already. Speaking of moving, this dog has the right idea.&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_0362.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0362&#34;&gt; In my last update, I told the story of my turning down a job opportunity at a company helping out the lovely, enchanting porn industry. In this episode of dubious job opportunities, I met with some dudes probably somewhere around my age in a fancy office in Scottsdale, and they told me tells of riches and a new cryptocurrency. Basically they&amp;rsquo;re a marketing company wanting to create their own cryptocurrency and use their marketing department to advertise it and make millions or something. My job would be to create simple advertising webpages and essentially copy bitcoin&amp;rsquo;s open source code, with the promise of 1% of the &amp;ldquo;mine&amp;rdquo; in addition to the 70k salary. Honestly, I seriously considered it, not because I&amp;rsquo;m particularly interested in get-rich-quick-schemes, but it&amp;rsquo;s more that I&amp;rsquo;m starved for something interesting to do. I&amp;rsquo;m not afraid to get another job if and/or when the gravy train stops or more likely, I find out there&amp;rsquo;s no gravy in the first place. I had my finger on the trigger and was about to accept the job, but I just felt sick. Was it cowardice, or was it rational thinking and prudence finally kicking in? I do know I wasn&amp;rsquo;t very thrilled with working in an environment where people seem to only care about money. I&amp;rsquo;ll never know what would have happened. I just hope this wasn&amp;rsquo;t my only chance to throw caution to the wind and actually do something interesting.  Or maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll have safe, boring jobs for the rest of my life. First World Problems, amirite? God Bless America. Have some pictures with no context: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_2693.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_0368.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0368&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_3995.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;                                           &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_1342.jpg?w=702&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_0396.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_2214.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_1261.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;   &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_6870.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt; Emily did some charity work and gave an ice cream code to the local homeless guy. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_2313.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt; Oh, our stake received a surprise visit from Jeffrey R Holland, who had come down for a funeral during his weekend that he had off. There is a mission president in our stake who had a daughter in her 30&amp;rsquo;s who unexpectedly passed away and left behind a husband and children. His main message, at least what I got out of it, was words of encouragement for those going through difficult times, in the eloquent, powerful way that is unique to Jeffrey R Holland. Well, I even hate to bring it up, but we moved. Again. We hired movers because we&amp;rsquo;re tired of moving things. We found a nice three bedroom house to rent in Phoenix, and that means that we can finally get a dog!! Also, we kind of live in the ghetto. It&amp;rsquo;s interesting over in our part of the world. But hey, we live close to this place where the rawk happens: &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_0390.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt; (featured, Dead To Me with lots of excited yelling people) Also I saw US Bombs. The US Bombs are fronted by a former pro skater who now hobbles around with a cane. If anyone has seen The Other F Word (highly recommended documentary about rockers coping with the responsibilities of fatherhood), he was the one who told the story of his son being hit by a car. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/u-s-bombs_seattle2017_-_by_olga_aguilar.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt; (not actual footage because I usually try and actually watch the show in real life instead of through a glowing rectangular screen) Emily has some interesting news about a web design job offer but I can&amp;rsquo;t tell you any more details because it&amp;rsquo;s the wrong month for the blog post. I can tell you she&amp;rsquo;s now doing a little bit of freelancing though. I think she might be interested in doing more freelancing, though I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to say that. Here are some weird pictures of Emily.                       &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_0401.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;                         &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/03/img_0400.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;                 &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_0361.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0361&#34;&gt;                               And here&amp;rsquo;s a weird picture of her foot. &lt;img src=&#34;https://dallincoons.files.wordpress.com/2018/02/img_0370.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMG_0370&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
        
    </channel>
</rss>
